#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/suman-gadhawal-bab941121 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python

C++

NumPy

# Suman Gadhawal

IITB | Machine Learning | Python

East Delhi, Delhi, India

## Summary

Experienced Python Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the industrial engineering industry. Skilled in Mathematical Modeling, Matlab, Python, Probability Theory, and Analytical Skills(Pandas,Matplotlib,Numpy,Decision Tree and random forecast,seaborn etc). Strong engineering professional graduated from Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay.

# Experience

Code Flow Tech LLP
Machine Learning Researcher
October 2018 - Present (1 year 6 months)
Noida Area, India

Romax Technology Software Developer May 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 5 months)

### Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay Master's degree, Mathematics · (2015 - 2017)